Levente Toth

Resume

0477 353 565 levthedev@protonmail.com Melbourne, VIC

Overview

Working as a network engineer for 5 years at Telstra, I pivoted in my 6th year into a development role in Test Automation.

While focusing on contributing libraries in Python for a brand new internal Test Automation framework which saved many hours of manual testing for Telstra, I taught myself C# and the Unity engine and released a mobile game to the Google Play store as a personal project, excited about and keen to learn as much as I could about software development.

I loved working in a collaborative team environment during my time at Telstra, in particular being able to share ideas and knowledge with the team to keep things moving or figuring out how to do things in a better way.

Realising what my true passion is through my new role at work and through personal projects at home, I have taken the plunge into a career change and completed an intensive course in Full Stack Web Development.

Skills

- Object Oriented Programming
- JavaScript, HTML, CSS/SCSS
- Git
- Ruby, Rails
- React/Redux, Node, Express
- Database Design
- PostgresQL, MongoDB
- Unit and Integration Testing
- Python
- Bash Shell and Scripting
- C# / Unity Engine

Education

- Diploma of Information Technology (Fast Track Web Development Bootcamp),
 Coder Academy 16 Feb 2020
- Bachelor of Electrical Engineering with Honours, University of Melbourne 16 Jul 2012

Experience

Serraview (Feb 2020 - Present)

I am currently undertaking a 1 month internship at <u>Serraview</u>. Here I am learning and experiencing what it takes to work in an Agile software team on a world leading corporate space management and optimisation solution. I am currently working in the migration team, converting the flagship product from the legacy Flash, .NET application into a modern React, Rails application.

Web Dev Bootcamp Projects (Aug 2019 – Feb 2020)

I recently completed the Coder Academy Fast Track Web Development bootcamp. The course focuses on modern web development with a practical approach. As part of the course I've been studying a number of web technologies including: HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Node.js, Express, NoSQL databases (MongoDB + Atlas), Ruby, Rails, SQL databases (PostgresQL), database design, Git, Agile methodologies, and unit and integration testing, giving me a broad introduction to key software engineering and product development skills.

Achievements

- Assignment: A small business website and Content Management System (CMS) for real world client business <u>Makeup by Ellie</u>. Made using the MERN stack (MongoDB, Express, React, NodeJS), collaboratively in a team of 3 using Agile project management and git workflow processes.
- Personal Project: Created <u>Grid Mage</u>, a webpage that procedurally generates CSS grid tiles of random dimension and aligns them perfectly with no gaps. I wrote the procedural generation algorithm from scratch.
- Personal Project: Organised, ran and taught a small workshop to teach a collaborative Git workflow with myself and four other classmates.
- Assignment: Created a dynamic website <u>Art Haus</u> in Ruby on Rails. Includes a PostgresQL database, AWS S3 file storage, authentication and authorization, payment processing, Google Maps API, integration testing and several other features.
- Assignment: Created a static <u>Portfolio</u> website in vanilla HTML and CSS. I focused on design and responsiveness.
- Assignment: Created a Terminal app <u>Objectmon</u> in Ruby, a Pokemon style game
 to explore the land and fight wild monsters with your monsters. Used Object
 Oriented approach to model players, map/map-tiles and monsters, included unit
 testing.

Telstra (Feb 2013 – 17th May 2019)

At Telstra I joined their graduate program, becoming a network engineer working for the Test Engineering team. For most of my time there I worked doing manual Routing and Switching network integration testing for many of Telstra's devices to help decide if a new piece of hardware or software was safe to deploy into production. In my last year at Telstra I convinced my manager to put me on the recently started Network Test Automation project. The project's goal was to create a framework and test suites that would allow the automation of simple and common regression tests. The framework was being built in Python and the test case scripts were written in Robot Framework calling methods from the framework libraries to emulate manual test steps.

Achievements

- Created several libraries and contributed to the framework codebase, covering different kinds of routing protocols and detection protocols (RSVP, BFD, QoS).
- Created many automated test scripts utilising my own libraries and the libraries created by others on the project (e.g. traffic generator control libraries).
- Given the Network Test Automation project still being in its early stages, I
 contributed to the code design best practices and our style guide to keep our
 libraries easily expandable and maintainable.
- Ran workshop/demonstration for the QoS library I created so that other testers can
 understand how to combine methods from my library and the test traffic control
 library into a Robot Framework test script to create QoS automated test cases.
- Through my contributions to the Test Automation project, I saved tens to hundreds
 of manual testing hours for many of the projects that are assigned to the Network
 Test Engineering team.

Game Development Personal Projects (Jun 2016 – June 2018)

I designed, started coding, and experimented with several different games. One of the games I wrote, "Hats", is a finished product. Hats is a mobile phone app designed to make the party game of the same name more streamlined and easier to both set up and play. Normally Hats uses pens, paper a stopwatch and a hat, this app was created to remove the need for all those items, as well as avoid some commonly faced issues that arose from human error. The Hats app was created in the Unity Engine using C#.

Achievements

- Created a design for how the app should work.
- Created a design for how the app should be programmed.
- Basics of Git, utilising BitBucket and GitKraken.
- Created Vector Graphics to create some graphics.
- Created the app, includes game itself, persistent settings, and monetization.
- Added animations.

Deployed to Google Play store.

University Capstone Project (June 2011 – Dec 2011)

As my Electrical Engineer Degree's Capstone Project, my project partner and I created a Remote Water Depth Gauge. Its purpose was to be able to respond to a text message from a mobile phone and with a text message containing the water level. It used an ultrasonic sensor, a GSM unit and a solar panel for power, all managed by a microcontroller chip.

Achievements

- Programmed the microcontroller to allow SMS communication between the Remote Water Depth Gauge and any mobile phone device, using C++.
- Programmed microcontroller to drive the ultrasonic sensor and retrieve data.

Portfolio

Please visit my portfolio site, <u>www.levtoth.dev</u>, to see my latest projects.